b'<!DOCTYPE html PUBLIC "-//W3C//DTD XHTML 1.0 Transitional//EN" "http://www.w3.org/TR/xhtml1/DTD/xhtml1-transitional.dtd">\n<html xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">\n<head>\n<meta http-equiv="Content-type" content="text/html;charset=UTF-8" />\n<meta name="viewport" content="width=460" />\n<title>is.gd - URL disabled</title>\n<meta name="keywords" content="URL disabled,disabled,v.gd" />\n<meta name="description" content="URL disabled" />\n<link rel="stylesheet" type="text/css" href="/isgd.css" media="screen" />\n<link rel="shortcut icon" href="/isgd_favicon.ico" type="image/x-icon" /></head><body>\n<div id="disabled"><h2>Link Disabled</h2><p>This shortened URL has been disabled due to a violation of our <a href="terms.php">terms & conditions</a>. Most likely this link was being used maliciously or was used in spam. Please be careful when visiting links you receive from somebody you don\'t know.</p><p>If you received spam, please be aware that we did not send it - is.gd is a URL shortening/redirection service and does not operate any email servers or lists. We have no contact with or association with spammers so are unable to unsubscribe you from any such lists.</p><p>is.gd takes all abuse of our service very seriously and we use a combination of automated measures and manual investigation of all complaints to prevent it wherever possible. Please see our <a href="spam.php">policy on fighting spam</a> for more details. We are sorry for any inconvenience that the misuse of this URL may have caused you.</p><p>For reference and to help those fighting spam the original destination of this URL is given below (we strongly recommend you don\'t visit it since it may damage your PC): -<br />ftp://<a href="/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection" class="__cf_email__" data-cfemail="33475b56415244575a5647735c5d5644524a405b5c43435a5d541d505c5e">[email&#160;protected]</a>:<a href="/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection" class="__cf_email__" data-cfemail="eb9f8e989fab8d9f9bc584858e9c8a929883849b9b82858cc5888486">[email&#160;protected]</a>/index.html</p><h2>is.gd</h2><p>is.gd is a free service used to shorten long URLs. For further information or to contact us (for example if you think this URL was disabled in error) please visit our website at <a href="https://is.gd/">https://is.gd/</a>.</p></div>\n<script data-cfasync="false" src="/cdn-cgi/scripts/5c5dd728/cloudflare-static/email-decode.min.js"></script></body>\n</html>'